THE UNCANNY COUNTER 2
《驅魔麵館2》
Just you wait. It's my turn now.
好好期待，現在開始輪到我了
Let's end it now.
來做個了結吧
No!
不行
Do-hwi.
導輝
Wake up, Do-hwi.
導輝，醒醒
Stay with me, Do-hwi.
導輝，你醒醒
What's the matter?
怎麼了？
You wanted to end things.
不是說要做個了結嗎？
Mr. Hwang.
黃老師
I guess you missed me after all.
看來你還是想念我
First,
首先
let me kill her. Then I'll compliment you.
讓我殺了那女的，再來好好疼愛你
I thought we'd be together forever.
我還以為我們會永遠在一起
What are you doing?
你在做什麼？
If you're adamant about leaving me, then there's nothing I can do.
既然妳堅持要離開我，那也沒辦法
But you're too precious for me
但就這樣把妳交給那群傢伙
to just hand over to them.
不是太可惜了嗎？
Damn it.
該死的
So?
所以呢？
Are you going to kill me and then consume me?
你要殺了我、吃掉我嗎？
Just think that you'll be living inside me.
想成妳在我體內活著吧
Thanks for your power in advance.
我會好好使用妳的能力的
Do-hwi.
導輝
She said she was nearby.
她說她在這附近
There!
那裡
Ha-na!
哈娜
Please save him.
拜託救救導輝
Please save Do-hwi!
拜託救救他
What happened?
怎麼會這樣？
So now there's conflict between those two.
意思是他們兩個人之間出了問題
Mr. Hwang and that woman, Gelly.
黃老師跟那個叫加利的女人
By the way, Mr. Hwang, I mean…
話說回來，黃老師…不對
Pil-gwang, was it?
他叫做必曠吧？
Isn't it a good thing that he and Gelly are fighting?
那傢伙跟加利打起來的話 對我們而言不是好事嗎？
Let one foe take the other out.
就像是以夷制夷
No. It may seem favorable right now.
不，雖然現在看起來是好事
But if he kills her and absorbs her power,
但若黃老師殺了那女人 吸收了她的力量與能力
he may become too powerful for us to summon.
我們反而可能會失去召喚的機會
Ha-na couldn't locate them, could she?
哈娜沒說過讀取到他們的位置吧？
It was a dangerous situation. She was up against two evil spirits.
因為當時情況很危險 甚至還有兩個惡鬼
Had she not used psychokinesis,
若哈娜姐沒使用念力
she likely wouldn't have escaped with Do-hwi.
很難跟導輝哥一起逃出來
We searched the entire city.
我們翻遍了整個重津市
So why couldn't you sniff them out?
為何你從未聞到過他們的氣味呢？
I'm doing my utmost best.
我真的已經盡全力了
What's wrong with my nose?
我的鼻子是怎麼回事？
Is it still not working properly?
偶爾還是會出問題嗎？
Tell me.
你說
You're cleaning your nostrils regularly, right?
你有按時清理鼻孔吧？
You bet. I even plucked out my nose hairs.
當然了，我連鼻毛都拔光了
-Hey. -Yes?
-喂 -什麼？
Why did you do that?
你怎能拔掉鼻毛？
Don't you know you need them to smell properly?
要有那個才能好好聞到氣味啊
-Seriously? -Hey, let me see.
-真的嗎？ -喂，讓我看看
How much you pluck?
你到底拔了多少？
-All of them. -They're all gone.
-全拔掉了 -全拔掉了呢
I thought the nose hairs were getting in the way.
我以為鼻毛會阻擋氣味
He'll be okay.
他會沒事的
Let's keep an eye on him and take him home before it gets late.
先觀察一陣子，別太晚送他回去
Thank you, Ms. Chu.
謝謝妳，秋女士
As for his memory, I erased all memories of Gelly.
關於他的記憶 我先刪除了加利那女人的部分
But won't he be flustered when he wakes up?
但等他醒過來後不會慌張嗎？
He won't remember anything.
因為記憶突然中斷
I'll try my best to sort that out.
我會好好收拾善後的
So he won't be startled when he wakes up.
讓他醒過來後不會嚇到
I'll settle everything.
我會全部都處理好的
Everything?
全部？
Ha-na.
哈娜
Do-hwi, are you awake?
導輝，你醒了嗎？
No, you can't get up yet. Lie down.
不，你還不能起來，躺著
What happened?
怎麼回事？
Where am--
這裡是哪…
What happened to your face?
妳的臉怎麼了？
My memory is vague.
我記不太起來
I remember that you were in danger.
我記得妳遇到危險
You're right.
沒錯
You saved me.
你救了我
You are pretty healthy.
你的身體的確很健康
You just…
只是…
got into…
遇上了一個
a small accident.
小型意外
You collapsed while trying to save me.
你為了救我而暈過去了
Thankfully, it happened near my place, so I brought you here.
幸好我就住在那附近 所以把你帶過來了
There was an accident?
出了意外嗎？
Do-hwi, remember that restaurant…
導輝，之前不是…
that we wanted to go to, but couldn't?
有間我們想去卻沒去成的餐廳嗎？
Yes.
對
I'd like to go there.
我想去那裡
Really?
真的嗎？
You booked tickets to a play too on the day.
你當時不是說你還買了話劇門票嗎？
Right?
對吧？
-I'll book them this time. Let's watch it. -No, let me.
-我會先買好，我們也去看吧 -不，我買就好
Are we really going together?
真的要一起去嗎？
I can't believe you're saying that.
沒想到能聽到妳說這種話
It just feels so surreal.
真的像做夢一樣
Meeting you…
再次遇見妳也是
and seeing you smile once again.
看見妳再次笑了的樣子也是
I actually prayed every day…
其實我每天都在祈禱
that I'd meet you again.
希望能見到妳
It was a short time, but I…
雖然時間短暫，但…
I was extremely happy thanks to you.
多虧了你，我非常幸福
Okay.
好
You'll feel better after taking a nap.
睡一覺起來就會舒服多了
You won't be in danger because of me anymore.
也不會再因為我而遇到危險了
Thank you for everything.
謝謝你，導輝
Damn it.
可惡
Damn it!
可惡！
Hwang Pil-gwang.
黃必曠
What should I do with you so I can stop feeling shitty?
我該怎麼做才能紓解這份不爽呢？
Damn it.
可惡
I can't believe that bitch became useful.
沒想到那個賤貨竟然派上用場了
She rose from the dead.
重生的女人
That means she got her power then.
這表示她也是在那時獲得力量的
What did she accept to come back to life?
她究竟是接受了什麼才復活的呢？
Damn it.
可惡
I won so many.
夾了真多呢
DO RE MI FA SOL LA TI DO CLASSIC PIANO ACADEMY
（DO RE MI FA SOL LA TI DO 古典鋼琴學院）
Mr. Park.
老師
Hello.
妳們好
Mr. Park, I practiced a ton.
老師，我練習了很久
No, I practiced more than you.
不對，我練習了更久
I practiced more than 1,000 times.
我練習了超過1000次
I practiced more than 2,000 times.
我練習了超過2000次
-No way! -That many times?
-才不是 -2000次？
Gosh.
天啊
Is Ha-na still not here yet?
哈娜還沒回來嗎？
Breakfast is almost ready.
早餐都快準備好了
I'm worried about her.
我很擔心哈娜
It won't be easy to forget him.
要整理心情並不容易
She looked so happy when she was with him.
她跟導輝哥待在一起時看起來很開心
She seemed to like him a lot too.
她好像也很喜歡導輝哥
Right.
對
What are you wearing?
那是怎樣？
Are you going somewhere? Why are you all dolled up this morning?
你要去哪嗎？ 一大早就穿得像是要去相親
I'm not.
沒有
This is how I normally dress. You don't know me at all.
我平常就是這樣穿 你完全不了解我呢
By the way, where's Ha-na?
不過沒看到哈娜呢
Jeez.
真是的
Gosh, you're savage.
天啊，你這狠毒的人
Look at you.
看看你
Do you take her sadness as an opportunity?
喂，她的悲傷是你的機會嗎？
You're more calculating than I thought.
仔細一看，你挺講究戰略的呢
You are.
講究戰略
Jeok-bong!
蹟逢哥
What is it?
怎麼了？
Take that off this instant.
立刻脫掉這件衣服
Why?
為什麼？
I'm worried it'll remind Ha-na of Do-hwi.
我怕哈娜姐看到這個會想起導輝哥
Those musical notes…
這些音符…
-Hurry. -Would she really, though?
-快 -真的會那樣嗎？
Ms. Chu.
秋女士
Let's not eat that today.
今天別放這道菜吧
Why not?
這道菜怎麼了？
Doraji and Do-hwi start with a D.
這是桔梗，開頭子音跟“導”一樣
That's not good. I'll take it away.
這可不行，我把它拿走
Do you really have to?
需要做到這地步嗎？
Then should we take this away too?
那麼這道菜也不能上桌吧？
It looks like a keyboard.
這看起來像是鋼琴鍵盤
-No. -Take that away.
-不行 -這個也拿走
In that case, why are we having chicken soup?
這樣講的話，今天為何要吃蔘雞湯？
It'll make her think of the dish we had that day.
這會讓她想起我們上次一起吃的雞湯
-No. -You're right.
-不行 -沒錯
Sorry, I'm late.
抱歉回來晚了
-Hey! -She's here!
-喂 -她回來了
Hey!
喂
What's wrong with you guys?
你們怎麼了？
-My back is killing me. -Are you okay?
-我的腰好痛 -妳的腰沒事嗎？
-I'll get changed. -Okay.
-我馬上去換衣服 -好
What's wrong with your back?
妳的腰怎麼了？
-Gosh. -What is it?
-天啊 -什麼？
Did someone come in?
有人來了嗎？
Hurry!
快
Hey, take them away.
喂，快把它們拿走
Didn't you say we were having chicken soup today?
今天原本不是說要吃蔘雞湯嗎？
Well, you see…
這個嘛，所以說…
Mo-tak has been craving ramyeon since this morning.
因為模度一大早突然說想吃泡麵
That's why. Right?
所以才準備這個，對吧？
Why did you…
為什麼要這樣呢？
Right.
對
There are days when you wake up and you crave ramyeon.
偶爾也會有一早就想吃泡麵的日子
Right?
對吧？
What? Right.
什麼？對
By the way,
對了
-the air feels so fresh this morning. -It sure does.
-今天早上心情真舒爽呢 -的確是
On a day like this, we should listen to some music.
這麼舒爽，得聽點舒爽的音樂吧
-Yes. -Yes.
-好
-Let's listen to some music while we eat. -Right.
-吃泡麵就是要聽音樂 -對
Cue the music.
打開音樂
Turn that off!
關掉
That's enough. I'm okay.
你們可以停止了，我沒事
Don't lie.
怎麼會沒事？
-When it comes to love-- -It's not like that.
-愛情這回事… -不是那樣的
Do-hwi will be okay too.
導輝也會沒事的
And I'll be okay.
我也沒事
So don't worry about me.
所以你們不必擔心我了
If you're really okay,
若妳真的沒事
-then can we have the chicken-- -Come on.
-我們可以吃雞湯了嗎？ -真是的
Right.
對了
The evil spirits' hideout…
惡鬼的藏身處…
Were you able to read something?
妳有讀取到什麼嗎？
It wasn't clear.
雖然不太清楚
But their hideout…
但他們的藏身處
looked a little too clean and tidy.
沒有久居的痕跡，非常乾淨
It felt like a luxurious resort or a hotel.
像是高級渡假村或飯店
I don't smell anything.
我沒聞到任何氣味
There are hotels elsewhere too.
這裡到處都是飯店
Let's check them one by one.
一間間去找吧
One by one?
一間一間找？
While Mo-tak looks for Lee Chung-jae,
在模度大叔找李忠宰的期間
we need to look for Hwang Pil-gwang.
我們必須找到黃必曠那傢伙
That lunatic is a monster.
那瘋子是怪物
He's a crazy monster.
徹底瘋掉的怪物
That I can agree.
他的確是怪物
But why did that monster come looking for you?
但那怪物為何會找上你呢？
Weren't you Lee Chung-jae's medical examiner?
你是負責幫李忠宰驗屍的醫師吧？
Did Ma Ju-seok come for you…
馬主席之所以找上你
because of Lee Chung-jae?
難道是因為李忠宰嗎？
That's the only thing you two have in common.
你跟馬主席之間的連結只有李忠宰
I don't know.
我不知道
I don't know anything!
我什麼都不知道
Please…
拜託…
Please capture that monster.
拜託抓住那怪物
Please help me.
拜託救救我
You're still playing dumb?
你還要裝無辜嗎？
I know you forged the autopsy result!
你不是偽造了驗屍報告嗎？
I know that Lee Chung-jae…
李忠宰
is still alive.
還活著啊
You also took part in creating that monster.
那個怪物也是你製造出來的
Do you know that?
知道嗎？
Hi.
嗨
How much is their rate again?
你說他們怎麼收費？
It's 200,000 won per hour, sir.
每小時20萬韓元
Jeez, the minimum wage has skyrocketed.
天啊，最低時薪調漲真多
Don't you agree?
對吧？
Do you guys even pay taxes?
他們要繳稅嗎？
I think they'll do a better job at losing the cops than our boys did.
但若要甩開警察 他們絕對比我們的人厲害
You idiot. We don't have any boys.
你這臭小子，我們哪還有人？
They've all been either killed or arrested.
要嘛死了，要嘛被關了
If you did your job properly
要是你有好好做
I wouldn't have to waste my money on these foreigners.
我何必浪費外幣，臭小子？
I'm sorry, sir.
對不起，會長
I'm already mad that I had to spend my money elsewhere.
一直浪費錢，我早就覺得快心疼死了
Gosh.
天啊
Hey, how is plan B going?
喂，準備好備案了嗎？
It's going well. All we need now is for you to tell us the date.
是，只要給我日期 你就能立刻出去了
Ga Mo-tak, was it?
他叫做賈模度嗎？
I should get rid of the scumbag who got in my way.
就算要出去，也得先除掉礙事的傢伙
Damn it.
真是的
What? Here.
什麼？喂
Hey, Lim Jae-youl.
嘿，林在悅
Long time, no see.
好久不見了
Good job. You may go.
辛苦了，你們可以走了
Sir.
會長
Hey, how have you been?
你過得好嗎？
Damn it. It must be rough for you.
該死的，你肯定很辛苦
It really wasn't me, sir.
真的不是我，會長
I don't know that cop or why that lady kept following me.
我不認識那警察 也不知道那大嬸為何要跟著我
Please spare me.
求你饒我一命
I ran away from the site by accident.
我真的只是偶然逃離現場而已
I know.
我知道
I know, okay?
我知道，好嗎？
I know you weren't digging your own grave.
你又不打算自尋死路
You wouldn't do that.
當然不可能會那樣做
-Right? -You're right, sir.
-對吧？ -對，會長
I've been loyal--
我對你忠心…
But still,
但是
you have to clean up your own mess.
你必須收拾自己的爛攤子
Sorry?
什麼？
He left the door unlocked.
他又沒鎖門就出去了
GRANDMA'S DEATH ANNIVERSARY
（奶奶忌日）
Why are you here?
大嬸，妳搞什麼？
Why are you back?
妳為什麼又來這？
Your house is so messy.
你這小子，家裡亂成這樣
Leave this instant.
快點出去
Gosh.
真是的
Jeez.
天啊
You must think I'm a joke since you can fight.
大嬸，妳或許因為 自己挺能打的就瞧不起我
But do you see this knife scar?
但妳看到這道刀疤了吧？
I can go haywire when I see red.
要是殺紅了眼，我也會不顧一切
Do you know that?
知道嗎？
Please.
拜託了
Please stay alive.
拜託活下來
Let me see.
讓我看看
It was my first time, so it still left a scar.
因為是第一次嗎？留下傷疤了呢
I thought I had gotten rid of it all.
我還以為我已經清理乾淨了
What?
什麼？
Aren't you hungry? Sit down.
你餓了吧？坐下
You should go.
妳出去
INCENSE STICKS
（香）
Is today the anniversary of your grandmother's death?
今天是你奶奶的忌日嗎？
Here.
給妳
Gosh, this is unlike you.
天啊，怎麼回事？
Gosh, that's refreshing.
天啊，真清爽
We don't need all this food.
不需要這些東西
The only thing my grandma needs is makgeolli.
反正我奶奶只要一杯馬格利酒就飽了 根本不吃其他東西
Do you miss her?
你想她嗎？
Have this.
吃這個
What's wrong with you? Are you nuts?
幹嘛這樣？妳瘋了嗎？
Have some food and eat with her.
吃吧，別讓奶奶一個人吃飯
It's tasty, right?
好吃吧？
How did you get that scar…
你肚子上的傷
on your stomach?
是怎麼造成的？
It's obvious.
還能是為什麼？
I was in a knife fight.
當然是揮舞刀時弄到的
A kid I know was stabbed while saving someone.
我認識的某個孩子為了救人 替對方挨了一刀
Why would he be an idiot and do such a thing?
他為何要那樣做？跟笨蛋一樣
His body probably reacted before he could even think.
他應該是不自覺地就挺身而出了吧
He had a kind heart.
因為他是心地善良的孩子
So?
所以呢？
What is he doing now?
那孩子現在怎麼樣了？
He's probably dead.
肯定死了吧
Nosy people tend to die early.
愛管閒事的人都早死
You're wrong.
不對
He's alive and well.
他活得好好的
Life isn't all that unfair.
這世界不是只有骯髒
There are more good people than bad ones.
有壞人，也有更多好人
But you just don't know that.
你只是傻傻地不知道這一點
To live…
只要好好活…
Goodness. What's wrong with me?
天啊，我是怎麼了？
Don't…
你…
Don't tell me you…
你該不會…
I'm sorry, lady.
對不起，大嬸
But I need to live.
我也得活下去
Why did you have to come back here?
所以誰叫妳又要出現？
Hello.
你好
It's me, sir.
是我，會長
We're ready.
已經準備好了
We'll finish off that cop too.
等把那個刑警也解決掉之後
Then, we leave.
我們就會撤退
Yes, sir.
是，我知道了
Unbelievable.
該死的
He wants me to cut their rate.
他叫我跟他們殺價
Are you awake, lady?
大嬸，妳醒了？
Who's that cop you're close to?
妳跟某個警察很熟吧？
-Mo-tak? -Yes, Ga Mo-tak.
-模度？ -對，賈模度
Tell him to come here right now.
叫他過來這
Then I'll spare you.
那麼我就放妳一馬
You want him to come here?
叫模度到這裡？
You heard me, hurry up.
既然聽懂了就動作快
They charge us by the hour.
那些傢伙以時間計費
It's a hefty sum.
很花錢
Are you sure?
真的要叫他來？
You'll regret it.
你會後悔的
Call him.
打給他
-Hey, Ms. Chu. -Mo-tak, it's me.
-妳好，秋女士 -模度，是我
-I need you to come here. -Here?
-你得過來這裡一趟 -“這裡”？
Where exactly are you? I'm busy searching all the golf courses.
“這裡”是哪裡？ 我很忙，還得調查高爾夫球場
Yes, I know. But I need you to come here.
對，我知道，但你得先來這裡
It's an emergency.
這裡也很急
Mo-tak.
模度
Come on. That's enough.
拜託，別這樣
Come on. Why are you doing this?
真是的，為什麼要這樣呢？
Why are you causing a scene in our country?
在別人的國家，這是在做什麼？
No, put that down.
不，把那個放下
No. Go over there, okay?
不，你過去，好嗎？
I get that it's hard to make money, but still.
就算賺錢很難，這也太超過了
-What are you? -What's that?
-這傢伙是怎樣？ -你叫我嗎？
Hey, stay back!
喂，別動
Move an inch and she's dead!
你要是敢動，這大嬸就會死
So? Are you going to rest some more?
怎麼樣？妳要多休息一會嗎？
I'm good. I've rested enough.
不，我休息夠了
I told you that you'd regret it.
我說過你會後悔的
What are you? You're not human, right?
你們是什麼東西？不是人吧？
It's scumbags like you who aren't humans.
你們這種傢伙才不是人
This will probably kill you, right?
這棍打下去，你會死吧？
Put your hands up, you scumbags.
手舉高，你們這些臭小子
-Put them up. -Put your hands up.
-手舉高 -叫你們把手舉高
Listen to me.
聽話
Did Lim Jae-youl hand you over to them?
是林在悅把妳交給這群傢伙的嗎？
I guess it's easy to turn evil, but not the other way around.
看來變壞容易，要脫離卻很難
You're wrong.
不對，秋女士
This is a blessing in disguise.
轉禍為福
I think he repaid your kindness in a way.
那傢伙也算是在報恩呢
What do you mean?
這是什麼意思？
Put your hands up properly!
臭小子，不把手舉好嗎？
We should take him to Lee Chung-jae.
我們應該帶著他一起去找李忠宰
It's not my fault.
不是我的錯
It's her fate that she crossed paths with me.
牽扯上我這種人，是那個大嬸命不好
Who are you?
你是誰？
I was right.
沒錯
Lee Chung-jae is a dead man.
現在李忠宰已經是死人了
You delivered Lee Chung-jae's money.
你就是替李忠宰送錢的那傢伙
Lee Chung-jae…
李忠宰
Where is he?
在哪？
An abandoned golf course?
停業的高爾夫球場？
He closed down a perfectly fine golf course and is going to town.
他關閉了一間好好的高爾夫球場 自己過著快樂似神仙的日子
Damn it.
該死的
PRESIDENT LEE
（會長）
You know what you need to say, right?
不需要教你該怎麼做吧？
Hello, sir.
是，會長
Why the hell are you taking so long?
你這小子為何不快點回來？
What is it? Is there an issue?
怎麼了？出了什麼問題嗎？
No, sir. We got rid of them.
不，已經處理得乾淨俐落
We're almost there.
快到了
Why the long face, you punk.
別愁眉苦臉，臭小子
We're going there to save him.
我們現在要去救你家會長
What? You shouldn't do that.
什麼？那樣不行
What do you mean?
你在說什麼？
I'll be his first target if he lives.
李忠宰活著的話會先解決我
Why don't you just kill him off this time around?
請你們趁這次幹掉李忠宰那小子吧
Jeez. This is unbelievable.
真是的，管理得還真好
Jeez.
天啊，那傢伙
-Please kill him. -Shut it, you idiot!
-拜託殺了他 -安靜點，小子
What's with his voice?
那小子的聲音是怎麼回事？
Damn it. He has no patience or spirit.
該死的，那小子既沒毅力也沒魄力
He better have reduced their rates.
他要是沒殺價成功就試試看
Calm down, Chung-jae.
沉著點，忠宰
What? Damn it.
什麼？該死的
What are you doing?
愣著做什麼？
Sir?
什麼？
Why aren't you retrieving it?
去撿球啊，發什麼呆？
You gave me the wrong club and see what happened.
不就是因為妳挑錯桿子 才會變成這樣的嗎？
But sir, how can I go in…
會長，但我要怎麼去那邊？
I'll bring you a new ball.
我準備其他球吧
Damn it!
該死的
Is everyone out to annoy me today?
大家今天都在跟我開玩笑嗎？
Do you know how much that costs?
妳知道那一顆球要多少錢嗎？
It costs 5,000 won!
5000韓元
Hey, lady. Go get the ball.
大嬸，把球撿回來
Go get my ball!
去把我的球撿回來
I'm sorry, sir.
對不起
You're sorry?
“對不起”？
Do you think that'll cut it?
道歉就行了嗎？
This won't do.
該死的，沒辦法了
Hey, come here.
喂，妳過來
I'll make a hole-in-one with your head, so stay still.
我要用妳的頭來打出一桿進洞，別動
-I was wrong, sir. -No.
-我錯了，會長 -不
You did nothing wrong. Just do better from now on.
妳沒做錯事，大嬸 現在起好好做就行了
This is perfect.
這樣剛剛好
Hey, give me a ball.
喂，拿球來
Nice. Okay, put your head down.
好，很好，低一點
Stay still.
可惡，別動
This is perfect. Stay still.
這樣剛剛好，別動
This is good.
就這樣，位置很好
Who the hell was that?
是哪個傢伙？
What's going on?
怎麼回事？
What the hell?
這是怎樣？
Who the hell is he?
那傢伙是誰？
Who is he?
他是誰？
I think he's that prisoner who escaped.
他好像是那個逃獄犯
-What? -The one on the news.
-什麼？ -新聞上的那個
The prisoner? The one who killed Mr. Park?
逃獄犯？殺了朴先生的那小子？
-Yes. -Ma Ju-seok, was it?
-對 -馬主席，對嗎？
Even the police couldn't find me and that guy did.
連警察都找不到我 那小子卻找到我了
Hey!
喂
It's nice to meet you, Ma Ju-seok!
見到你很開心，馬主席
You already killed your wife's murderer,
殺掉殺死你老婆的傢伙不就夠了嗎？
Why the hell would you bother coming here?
為什麼還來找我撒野？
I--
我…
Come on. Do your money's worth.
喂，還在做什麼？不工作嗎？
He doesn't have fond feelings for me. Hurry…
那小子看起來對我不懷好意，快…
All right!
我知道了
I'll give you anything you want, okay? One billion? Two billion?
你想要多少我都給你，好嗎？ 10億韓元？20億韓元？
Fine, half. I'll give you half, okay?
好，一半，我給你一半，好嗎？
Thanks for being alive,
謝謝你還活著
so that I can kill you with my own hands.
讓我能親手殺了你
Stop!
住手
Help me.
救命
-Mo-tak! -Ms. Chu!
-模度 -秋女士
Take Lee Chung-jae with you and go!
快帶李忠宰離開
Okay.
好
You bastard.
你這混帳
Come with me, you bastard.
跟我來，混帳
Get in, you bastard.
進去，混帳
Get these off.
解開這個
Get these off!
我叫你解開這個
I can't do that.
那可不行
It's unlike me to let go of an evil spirit.
要是讓惡鬼逃了，就不是賈模度了
You knew that Lee Chung-jae was alive.
你知道李忠宰還活著
You knew that Min-ji's killer
你知道折磨旼祉的混帳
was still alive and well, but hid it from me.
活得好端端的，卻瞞著我
And now, you're getting in my way?
然後現在還想阻止我？
We must stop you!
必須阻止你
We must before the evil spirit
必須在惡鬼
consumes you whole.
徹底吃掉你的身體之前阻止你
Stop here, Ma Ju-seok.
停下來，馬主席
Lee Chung-jae will receive his punishment.
李忠宰會受到懲罰的
Die!
殺了他
Kill everyone!
殺了所有人
What are you doing, Ma Ju-seok?
你在做什麼，馬主席？
You need to kill him!
必須殺掉他才行
And what makes you the ones to punish him?
為什麼是由你們來懲罰他？
You've lost your chance.
你們的機會結束了
Come on, lady.
搞什麼，大嬸？
Drive properly, will you?
該死的，好好開車
Ma Ju-seok, no!
馬主席，不行
Go away!
別過來
Please go away!
拜託別過來
I'm not done with you just yet!
還沒結束
Go away!
別過來，該死的
Mo-tak!
大叔
-Mo-tak. -Mo-tak!
-大叔 -模度
Ma Ju-seok did this?
是馬主席做的？
How could he?
他怎會做到這地步？
How pathetic.
令人心寒
You let Lee Chung-jae go.
竟然讓李忠宰從你眼前逃脫
I told you to get rid of those who got in your way.
我說過了 不能讓那群阻止你的傢伙活命
You must kill them all, Ma Ju-seok!
必須殺掉那群傢伙，馬主席
They could care less about my pain.
根本不在乎我的血淚
They were unhappy that I had this power.
那群傢伙只是看不順眼我擁有的力量
You'll soon realize that as well.
你很快也會理解的
If we want our revenge
為了我們的報仇
we'll need to kill them.
必須先殺掉那群傢伙
Hold still. Don't move.
好好待著，別動
Your bones are shattered.
骨頭全碎了
What do we do?
該怎麼辦？
It looks as if a tiger bit him.
像是被老虎咬了一樣
-Jeok-bong. -Yes?
-蹟逢 -是？
I'm not dead.
有人死了嗎？
You look so
你看起來
ugly right now--
好醜…
It's done.
行了
Thank you, Ms. Chu.
辛苦了，秋女士
I wonder what happened to Lee Chung-jae.
不知道李忠宰怎麼樣了
He's probably lying low again.
肯定又裝死躲起來了吧
He's one lucky scumbag.
該說李忠宰那傢伙運氣好嗎？
He ran away when Ma Ju-seok and Mo-tak were fighting each other.
偏偏趁馬主席跟模度前輩打鬥時 平安無事地逃掉了
But it's a relief, isn't it?
但這不是該慶幸的事嗎？
-Ma Ju-seok didn't get to kill him. -You're right.
-因為他沒被馬主席殺掉 -對
It's a shame that we lost both of them.
雖然被他們兩個人逃掉很可惜
But we stopped Ma Ju-seok from committing another murder.
但至少阻止了馬主席殺人
Let's not be discouraged.
所以大家打起精神吧
Also, Ma Ju-seok was only hostile toward the individual he resented.
而且，若不是自己怨恨的人 馬主席也不打算殺死他們
That's not guaranteed though.
這很難說
His rage has probably grown even bigger now.
因為這件事，馬主席肯定會更加憤怒
And that means the evil spirit has become stronger.
也就是說，惡鬼的力量會變得更強
GRANDFATHER
（外公）
Come on.
真是的
Jeez.
天啊
I promise that we'll go see him tomorrow.
我們明天一定會去見妳親愛的
You haven't been acting out lately. What's gotten into you?
好一陣子相安無事 妳怎麼又開始使性子了？
Grandma.
外婆
Hey.
嘿
Call my darling to come, will you?
叫親愛的來，我親愛的
Hey, come on.
嘿，老太婆
Let's go inside now.
我們進去吧
He said he'd visit tomorrow.
他說他明天會來
Grandma.
外婆
Mr. Ma…
大叔…
won't be coming anymore.
以後不會來了
Hey, Mun.
蘇炆
So you shouldn't be acting this way. Stop.
所以妳不能這樣做，別這樣子
No.
不
He said he'd come.
他說他會來
He said he would.
他說過他會來
He told me so.
他說會來
That's enough.
夠了，外婆
I miss that kind man
我也跟妳一樣
as much as you do.
非常想念那位善良的大叔
But Mr. Ma won't be coming anymore.
但他不會再來了
So stop.
所以別這樣了
We need to stop, Grandma.
我們必須停下來了，外婆
After all,
結果
it seems you've failed to kill Lee Chung-jae.
你沒能殺死李忠宰嗎？
I'm sure you've finally realized who was being truthful,
你現在想必明白了誰說的才是真話
who you should kill first for your revenge,
知道為了報仇，你必須先殺死誰
and if you don't give up,
而且只要你不停手
that they will kill you first.
他們就會先殺死你
I want to know how to get rid of them.
我想知道除掉他們的方法
Is that why you came to see me?
這就是你來找我的原因？
You want to fight against them?
你要對抗他們？
Yes.
對
You know something.
你肯定知道些什麼
You wouldn't have fought against them if there wasn't a way.
若是沒有辦法 你從一開始就不會和他們交手
This fight will only end once one party dies.
這場戰鬥，必須有一方死掉才會結束
It's either them
不論是他們
or us.
或是我們
So do you really have the guts to kill them?
不過你有信心殺死他們嗎？
You even spared that worthless doctor who forged
連把活得好好的李忠宰 變成死人的那個垃圾醫師
Lee Chung-jae's death.
也殺不死的你？
Do you really think a soft person like you…
懦弱的馬主席
can kill those who were once like family to you?
有辦法殺死曾被你視為家人的 那群傢伙？
Ma Ju-seok.
馬主席
How am I supposed to believe that?
這要我如何相信？
Like you said,
如你所說
I have no choice now.
我已經沒有選擇的餘地了
I must see through my revenge.
因為我非得結束這場復仇
I, Na Jeok-bong,
我羅蹟逢
believe that a true Counter should be of help when his colleagues are troubled!
是在其他驅魔人辛苦時 能成為他們力量的真正驅魔人
With that determination in mind, I must sniff them out once again.
憑著這個想法，鼻子逢要再次出動了
Jeok-bong,
蹟逢哥
what are you doing right now?
現在是什麼情況？
Mo-tak, have you seen Jeok-bong?
大叔，你沒看到蹟逢哥嗎？
Jeok-bong? No, I haven't.
蹟逢？我不知道
-Mun. -Yes?
-蘇炆 -是？
Do you want some coffee?
你要來杯咖啡嗎？
That was random.
這麼突然
I know it's unexpected.
你當然會感到意外
I normally ask others for coffee.
我通常都是討咖啡的那個人
This is the first time I'm making coffee for you.
這是我第一次泡咖啡給別人喝
I rarely serve coffee to others.
我很少幫別人準備咖啡
All right.
好了
Have some.
喝吧
It's nutty.
很香呢
-Right? It's nutty and tasty. -It is.
-對吧？又香又好喝吧？ -對
All right.
沒錯
There must be a reason why I made that for you, right?
我會給你咖啡，肯定有原因吧？
Excuse me?
什麼？
Mo-tak, you're overexerting yourself today.
大叔，今天的話太勉強了
You need some rest.
你先休息
You're wrong.
不
We always fought evil spirits, no matter our condition.
我們跟惡鬼打鬥時 會先考慮身體狀態嗎？
Blast me.
出拳試試
Are you okay?
大叔，你沒事嗎？
-What's that? -Nothing.
-你叫我嗎？ -沒有
Let's go. Do it harder!
來吧，再用力一點
Ma Ju-seok was much stronger than that.
馬主席的力量比這強多了
-But Mo-tak… -Mun.
-可是大叔… -蘇炆
I represent strength.
賈模度等於力量
If my psychokinesis won't work,
既然念力不行
then I should at least be able to withstand his.
至少得有力量能承受念力
I got this.
我可以的
I can do it.
我能辦到
Blast me again, Mun.
再次出拳吧，蘇炆
I'll go harder this time.
這次會更用力
Mun.
蘇炆
Gosh, that was too much.
天啊，為什麼這麼誇張？
Goodness.
天啊
Did you see that?
看到了吧？
Did you see how I withstood your psychokinesis?
喂，我突破你的念力
And then, I hit you.
攻擊你的樣子
Did you see that?
你看到了嗎？
I did.
看到了
Mo-tak, see?
喂，模度，看吧
Use your brain if you don't have the strength.
既然力量不行，至少要動腦筋
Mo-tak,
大叔
I told you to never let your guard down.
我說過不能掉以輕心了
Right, I shouldn't.
對，不能掉以輕心
Ma Ju-seok would've attacked you more ferociously than I did.
若是馬主席 肯定會攻擊得比現在更猛烈
Have you acknowledged him as a true evil spirit now?
你現在完全認同馬主席是惡鬼了嗎？
I have no other choice.
我別無選擇
If I want to protect everyone,
若要守護我們所有人
I must stay grounded and summon him at all costs.
我不能再動搖，絕對要召喚他才行
Before it's too late.
免得為時已晚
Hey!
小子
Do you think you're in this alone?
只有你一個人召喚嗎？
Didn't you see me just now?
你沒看到我剛才做的嗎？
You can trust me.
喂，你可以相信我
I'm no longer the Ga Mo-tak I used to be.
我已經不是以前的賈模度了
I smell something in Jungjin 2-ga!
在重津二街發現氣味
What?
什麼？
I've never smelled this intense smell before!
是第一次聞到的濃烈氣味
Intense smell?
濃烈氣味嗎？
That's right.
對
I'm smelling something near the hotels we searched!
我在我們找過的飯店附近聞到了氣味
But this smell doesn't belong to Mr. Hwang.
但這不是黃老師的氣味
It's Ma Ju-seok. He set foot.
是馬主席，他踏入了
-Where, Ha-na? -A hotel near Jungjin 2-ga.
-在哪裡，哈娜姐？ -重津二街附近的飯店
He's going inside.
他進入飯店了
A hotel?
飯店嗎？
-Jeok-bong. -What?
-蹟逢哥 -什麼？
I swear he came in here.
他明明進來這裡
But the smell is gone now.
但氣味消失了
It's gone?
氣味消失了？
Yes.
對
-Jeok-bong. -Yes?
-蹟逢 -是？
What about Mr. Hwang? Can you smell him?
黃老師呢？沒有他的氣味嗎？
No, I don't smell anything.
對，我沒聞到他的氣味
Hold on.
等等
Ha-na.
哈娜
He definitely pressed the top floor button.
他一定是按了最高樓層
Is this the tallest hotel in Jungjin?
這是重津最高的飯店嗎？
Yes.
對
We'll see the entire city from the top.
在上面肯定能俯瞰整座重津市
What's the matter?
你怎麼了？
The smell.
氣味
The smell is back.
氣味又出現了
It's the same smell from before.
我確定是剛才的那個氣味
It smells similar to fermented soybeans.
類似清麴醬的氣味
Out of the blue?
這麼突然？
The smell vanished, then reappeared?
消失的氣味突然又出現了？
And…
而且
there's another smell.
還有另一股氣味
I smell Mr. Hwang.
有黃老師的氣味
Do you mean those two are together?
你是說黃老師跟馬主席在一起嗎？
Yes, I'm sure of it.
對，肯定沒錯
We're getting closer…
兩股氣味
to both of them!
全都越來越近了
The height.
是高度
That's why the smell disappeared.
氣味消失的原因
Jeok-bong could only smell within a limited distance and height.
蹟逢哥的能力 不只受限於距離，也受限於高度
We couldn't find Mr. Hwang because he was here all along.
黃老師一直躲在這 所以我們才找不到他
I'm sure this is it.
絕對是這裡
I can't tell which direction since it's reeking so much.
氣味太濃了，我分不出方向
It's one of these.
是這邊的其中一間
Mun, summon the territory first.
蘇炆，先召喚領地
Okay.
好
What's wrong?
怎麼了，蘇炆？
Ms. Chu, it's just that…
秋女士，我只是…
I summoned the territory, but I can't see it.
我明明召喚了領地，卻看不到領地
What do you mean?
這是什麼意思？
You summoned it but you can't see it all of a sudden?
你召喚了領地，卻突然看不到它嗎？
It's not that you can't summon it, Mun. It just doesn't reach that high.
不是無法創造，蘇炆 領地到不了那高度
It doesn't reach?
領地到不了？
You must get out of there!
你們必須盡快離開那
You can't catch the evil spirits without the territory!
沒有領地，你們無法抓惡鬼
Hurry!
快
Hold on.
等等
Jeok-bong wasn't the only one whose power was limited?
能力受限的不只是蹟逢
There is a limit to the territory as well?
連領地也有極限嗎？
Hwang Pil-gwang.
黃必曠
So I really don't see it.
果然看不到呢
What you call…
你所召喚的…
the "territory", that you summon.
被你們稱為“領地”的那股氣息
You need it so much
你們那麼需要的東西
yet you can't have it here.
這裡卻沒有
On the other hand,
而我們
we don't need it.
不需要那個
We?
我們？
So you've come all this way.
結果你還是到了這裡
You followed me here.
追著我來到了這
I'm glad you're here.
很高興你們來了
This will be…
這裡
your gravesite.
將會成為你們的墳墓
What do we do now?
該怎麼辦？
There's no territory here.
這裡沒有領地
I'll take Ma Ju-seok.
我負責馬主席
We'll take Hwang Pil-gwang.
我們負責黃必曠
Ha-na.
哈娜
-Get up. -Ha-na.
-小心 -哈娜
I don't need the territory.
沒有領地也沒關係
I'm going to put an end to you and that bastard Hwang Pil-gwang today.
今天在這裡 我會了結你跟黃必曠那傢伙
That's right, Mun. There's nothing we can do about this.
對，蘇炆，已經別無他法了
Neither of us will regret this.
無論你我都不會後悔
Mun!
蘇炆
No.
不行
What's wrong?
怎麼了？
Surprised to see an unexpected guest?
不請自來的客人讓你們慌了？
Hold still.
別動
I knew it.
果然
You had it too.
你也有
A moment of rebirth.
重生的時刻
I'm not powerful enough to kill you.
靠我的力量難以殺了你
But how about this?
但如果是這樣呢？
What if I erased the memory
如果我刪除
of your rebirth?
你重生的時刻
What'll happen once the power
你靠這個獲得了力量
you've acquired
若它消失
disappears?
你會變成怎樣呢？
No!
不行
Mun!
蘇炆
Mun, stay with me!
蘇炆，醒醒啊
What have you done?
妳在做什麼？
It would've been a waste!
太可惜了啊
How could I let you take his power?
怎麼能把這傢伙的力量交給你？
THE UNCANNY COUNTER 2
《驅魔麵館2》
So Mun is in a coma.
蘇炆陷入昏迷狀態了
Please open your eyes, Mun.
蘇炆，拜託你睜開眼
His memory is completely gone.
他的記憶徹底消失了
I should at least consume their souls.
現在我至少得吃掉那群傢伙才行
We need to show him that he doesn't need to protect us
必須讓蘇炆看到我們不需要他的守護
and that we can protect him.
我們可以守護他
How does it feel to be attacked in the dark?
在黑暗中受到攻擊的心情如何？
Do you think this is the end?
你以為這就是結束了吧
Ji Cheong-sin?
池清臣？
You need to return to everyone who's waiting for you!
你必須回到大家等著你的地方啊
You're not alone, Mun.
你不是一個人，蘇炆
Believe in all the moments that we spent together.
相信我們在一起的那些時間
Subtitle translation by: Soo-ji Kim
字幕翻譯： 林欣儀